

#### **ABOUT ME**

I'm a junior game programmer specialized on object-oriented programming. Although I at my fourth year of university, I have already done a great variety of projects on my own, won several awards, done over 13 game jams and worked for two videogame companies. I'm a very enterprising person, outgoing and eager for new experiences.

#### CONTACT

636 98 24 40

Mataró, Barcelona

marina.chava24@gmail.com

Nationality: Spanish & Australian

Date of birth: 13/12/2000

Gender: Female

#### LINKS

#### Portfolio:

https://marinachavarria.netlify.app/

https://www.linkedin.com/in/marinachavarria-gonzalez/

# **Marina** Chavarria Gonzalez

## Junior game programmer

### WORK EXPERIENCE

MELBOT STUDIOS Jan. 2021 – Now

I work for Melbot as a junior programmer. Melbot is a videogame company that combines art and innovation to make games with a soul.

INTERSHIP AT KANEDA GAMES SL Jun. 2021 – Aug. 2021

I work for 3 months for unpublish project. I was with a programming team following their coding conventions, making physics, player controllers, AI, and making the game structure all the way from the menus to the game modes.

XNERGIC TECNOCAMPUS Oct. 2020 – Jan. 2021

I worked with Xnergic, a company which gives different technology curses during the year to children. I have done all the way from Unity and C# to Arduino.

#### **PROJECTS**

#### IT HAS TO BE YOU | UNITY GAME

July 2021

- Narrative puzzle for my third year final project.
- All the team work for three months to make the game. We did different puzzles systems and also an inventory system.

#### **CUBE'S SIDE! | UNITY MOBILE GAME**

September 2021

- A puzzle game with two game modes, one with linear levels and the other one with randomly generated levels.
- The game was created only by myself with Unity, and it has an Ads system and a progress saving system.

Over 10 games more on my Itch.io

#### GAME AWARDS

#### **CAECUS King Game Jam**

Overall best game – 2019

**BABY KING** IndieDevDay Game Jam Honourable mention – 2020

**CODEBOX Siemens Gamesa Hackathon** 

Second place - 2020

**WORLD CLASSATE Siemens Gamesa Hackathon** 

First place – 2021

#### **FORMATION**

#### **VIDEOGAME DESIGN | TECNOCAMPUS**

2018 - Currently studying

Im currently on my forth year studying videogames design at Tecnocampus Mataro.

#### **LANGUAGES**

English: High

Spanish: Native

Catalan: Native

#### **SKILLS**

- C#
- Lua

- Unity
- Defold R
- Unreal engine